嗨 大家好
Hello everyone.
让我们欢迎今天到公园的
We want to welcome a very special guest
特殊客人
to our park today
总统的女儿
the president's daughter.
笑笑 笑笑
Big smile. Big smile.
你好 亚历山德拉
Hello Alexandra.
你爸爸呢？
Where's your father?
他就要来了
He'll be here.
我倒要看他来不来
I'll make sure of it.
嗨 你好 小公主
Well hey there,little miss first lady,
我是丁克 这里的主人
I'm Dinky Winks owner of this fine establishment.
你要历险 惊声尖叫吗？
You ready to ride the ride and shrill to the thrills,spills and chills?
是 是的
Yes I am.
到这边来
Right this way!
当然 我身后的是世界著名的"搅打器"
Of course that behind me the world-famous Whippersnapper.
保证让成年人
Guaranteed to make grown men howl
象婴儿断奶时大叫
like a cub woke at weaning time.
在我们左边…
Over on our left...
"神经毁灭" 噢 痛苦哦
The NerveWracker oh-ho painful.
很好玩
Good fun.
再往左
On your other left
是我最喜欢的
is uh well,my personal favorite
"催吐器"
the Vomiter.
我们警告了大家
Now we tell people
吃太饱时不能玩这个
not to ride it on a full stomach,
但你知道他们
but you know folks.
他们都不会听的
They just don't listen.
但…
But...
干嘛理会这些呢？
why bother with any of those?
你来是为了玩最新的和最棒的
You're here for my latest and greatest.
为了让你玩得满意 玩得痛快
For your personal amusement and complete gratification,
我建议你玩…
I humbly offer...
魔术器
the Juggler.
它快吗？
But is it fast?
快吗？
Is it fast?
那我们看看 好吗？
Well let's see shall we?
乘者坐在圆顶舱里
The riders are strapped into the bubble.
超级机器人把圆顶舱送到高空
The hydrobot lifts the bubble high into the air.
让它旋转到政府允许的
And spins it round and round as fast
最高速度
as the United States government will allow.
圆顶舱旋转 变向 翻转 腾空
The bubble spins turns,flips and bounces.
然后… 它轮流抛接
And then...it juggles you.
我要玩这个
I want to go on!
我想你会的
I thought so.
这是 超驰控制装置 安全是最重要的
Now understand the override precautions are top-notch,
是我改装的
modified by yours truly.
我想她爸爸应该在场
I thought her father was supposed to be here.
总统有更重要的事
The president has more pressing business
而不会在主题乐园里
than to spend an entire Sunday
呆上整个星期天
in a theme park.
没人那么忙
No one's that busy.
玩好 孩子
Have fun kid.
我们把它调慢些
We'll take it a little slow,
让它更好玩
just make it fun.
能把她放下来吗？
Can't you get her down?
有人停了超驰控制
Somebody's jammed the override.
哦 这个惹事精
Why that little troublemaker.
冷静 冷静
Remain calm. Remain calm.
我们是特务人员 没有问题
We are the Secret Service. Everything is under control.
- 我们什么也做不了 - 怎么？
- There's nothing we can do sir. - What?
她站的地方摇摇晃晃
The weight of our agents will prevent us from ascending
我们特工的体重太大 不能去
the shaky precipice on which she now stands.
她会掉下来的
She'll fall.
我们没有小特工吗？
Don't we have any smaller agents?
带特工小子1号和2号
Bring me agents SK1 and SK2.
- 让让路 - 让让路
- Coming through. - Coming through.
我们准备好了
We're ready.
用这个最新装备
Use this the latest gear.
之后我们能留下吗？
We get to keep them afterwards?
不 不行
N-No.
可以
Yes.
当然可以
Of course.
开始吧
Let's rock.
你肯定他们能搞定吗？
You're sure they can handle this?
若不行 还有两人可以
If not,there are two others who can.
带特工小子3号和4号做后援
Bring me agents SK3 and SK4 as backup.
有人来了
We got company.
加利和杰蒂 他们来这里干什么？
Gary and Gerti what are they doing here?
对不起了 小子
Excuse me there sport.
你从哪里搞来的那个？
Where did you get that?
最新的电子升降技术
Latest in electro-riser technology,
用新的合成材料和人工智能控制
with new composite materials and A.I. brainology.
我知道
I can see
你听不懂我说的什么
you don't know what I'm talking about.
加利 这次由我救援
Gary this is my rescue.
我们从这里接手了
We'll take it from here.
"最新装备" 真没用
"Latest gear," my butt.
不 不 不
No no no!
你会搞得更糟
You'll just make it worse!
看你干的
Now you done it.
到这里
Over here!
一边去
Get away from me!
亚历山德拉 抓住我的手
Alexandra take my hand!
退后
Back off!
我要我爸爸来救我
I want my father to come up here and get me.
但他是美国总统
But he's the president of the United States.
不 他是我爸爸
No he's my father.
他在当总统前就是我爸爸
He was my father before he ever became president,
他现在还应该是我爸爸
and he should still be my father now.
我要他到这里来
I want him up here!
先生 有情况了
Sir we have a situation.
她拿了魔酷光碟
She's got the Transmooker.
是紧急情况
This is now a code-red situation.
快把她救下来
Get her down now!
问题是
The point is,
你和你爸爸该好好谈谈
you and your father need to have a talk.
这里并不是合适的地方
Up here may not be the best place.
跟我来 我向你保证
Come with me,and I promise you,
他会和你谈的
the two of you will have that talk.
你怎能做到？
How can you promise that?
我是二级人物
I'm Level 2.
我能命令他和你谈
I can order him to talk to you.
嗨 杰蒂
Hi Gerti.
在做什么？
Whatcha doing?
我想把魔术器停下
I'm trying to stop the ride.
- 不分离中轴？- 没错
- Without disengaging the axis? - Exactly.
那你就停手吧
Then stop what you're doing.
你看 魔术器就象个巨大的磁器
You see the ride is designed to work like a giant magnet.
若你对换两极
If you reverse the polarization,
总统的女儿就完了
bye-bye,president's daughter.
再见
See you around.
好的
Okay.
等等
Wait.
我今早从爸爸办公室拿了这个
I took this from my father's office this morning.
我肯定他要拿回
I'm sure he'll want it back.
小心
Careful!
克兹 你带她下去 我拿这个下去
Look Cortez you take her down,and I'll take this down.
这样 我们都好看
That way we both look good.
我并不是为了好看 加利
I'm not doing this for looks Gary.
谢天谢地 你没事吧 亚历山德拉
Thank goodness you're all right Alexandra.
我们可急坏了
We were worried sick.
嗨 伙计们
Oh boys.
我想你们在找这个
I think this is what you're looking for.
她从总统那里偷的
She swiped it from the president.
噢 你这回有大麻烦了 小姑娘
Oh you're in big trouble this time missy.
等等
Wait a minute.
我答应了她让她和总统讲话
I promised her she could talk to her father.
噢 她会的 好吗
Oh she'll talk to him,all right.
我们保证会的
We'll make sure of that.
- 答应我一件事 - 什么？
- Promise me one thing. - What?
再也不做这种出力不讨好的事了
No more ricky dicky thing on this
《非常小特务2》
(梦境岛)
那你想接受尤卡达任务 是吗？
So you want the Ukata assignment huh?
你的任务由特工处给你传达
Your duties are assigned to you by the agency
和其他人一样 和我一样
same as everyone,same as me.
我知道 这些我们已经学了很多了
I know. It's just that we've learned so much.
朱尼和我可以接受更重要的任务
Juni and I are more than capable of taking bigger assignments.
但这不由你来定
But that's not your decision to make.
特工小子这个组织组建不久
The Spy Kids organization is still new,
若你是3级人物甚至2级人物
and if you're a Level 3 or even a Level 2,
也不能单独执行任务
you cannot go on a mission alone.
你需多磨练
You need more experience.
怎么回事
Come on.
妈 若你找绝密情报
Okay Mom if you're looking for top-secret information,
可直接连接
just go straight to the source.
欢迎来到五角大楼
Welcome to the Pentagon.
你怎么做的？你不能这么做
How did you do that? You can't do that.
在家里不允许有黑客
There is no hacking in this household.
我知道 对不起
I know. Sorry.
教我怎么做
Show me that again.
我知道梳理头发是我的弱项
I know this hair thing is one of my weakest points.
等一会
Wait one minute.
你会很酷
You're gonna look cool.
事实上 你看起来更酷 对不？象我
In fact you're looking cooler,right? Like me.
像波比一样
Like Poppy.
对我而言有点特殊感觉
And it's kind of em-o-tion-al to me.
知道吗？
You know? Uh-oh.
打结了
A knot.
我们要…
We are gonna...
你…
You...
好了
Uh-huh uh-huh. We got it.
好孩子
That's my boy.
最后一下
Last touch.
要我给你打领结吗？
You want me to tie it for you?
不用 小绿瓢可以打
No it's okay. R.A.L.P.H. can do it.
蝴蝶结 小绿瓢
Bow tie R.A.L.P.H.,
不要太紧
and not too tight.
谢谢 小绿瓢
Thanks R.A.L.P.H.
有意思
Interesting.
但是…
But...
他永远也不能替代…
he can never ever replace...
我
me.
还不行 但我想
Not yet but I think
最新升级产品下周就到
that new upgrade comes in next week.
噢
Oh.
开个玩笑
Only joking.
孩子 孩子 孩子 孩子
Kids. Kids. Kids. Kids.
孩…
Ki-
玩笑？
Joking?
谢谢你
Thank you.
妈妈
Yes ma'am.
记住 孩子们
Okay. Remember kids,
今晚对你们父亲非常重要
this is a very important night for your father.
若他被选为 欧斯的主管
And if he's named director of the O.S.S.,
要站起来 给他个热烈拥抱
be sure to stand up and give him a big hug,
好吗？
all right?
若爸爸不能赢呢？
What if Dad doesn't win?
那 给他个更热烈拥抱
Well then,give him a bigger hug.
姚玲 王玲 欢迎来到…
Oh Yao Ling Wa Ling,
这是丹妮尔和迪安
this is Danielle and Dione Daluc.
- 你好 - 你好
- Hello. - Hi.
他们发明了信息连接 象在线交易系统
They created lnfolink sort of an online trading system
用于国际间的情报交换
for swapping international secrets.
嗨
Hi.
Oh hey.
你好
Hello.
香槟酒？
Champagne?
我不喝
Can't have any of that.
对不起
Sorry.
感觉有点不对头
Something doesn't feel right.
毫不奇怪 你的伙伴在这里
No wonder your buddy's here
你的伙伴 有奇怪的笑声
your buddy with the weird laugh.
他的笑声不奇怪
He does not have a weird laugh.
我们正在… 谈论你
We were just... talking about you.
真的吗？
Really?
你看来很棒 卡门
Wow. You look great Carmen.
- 想跳舞吗？- 当然
- You want to dance? - Sure.
我不认为那是个好主意 加利
I don't think that's a good idea Gary.
家规规定 你要征得我父亲的同意
Family rules say you need to ask my father's permission.
你的衣服应该剪掉 朱尼
You know you should have had that suit tailored Juni.
它都挤到你的肚子上了
It's bunching up around your gut,
那使你的脑袋看起来太大
and it makes your head look way too big.
请你原谅我弟弟
You have to excuse my little brother.
他还在为… 魔术器的事生气
He's still a little upset about the...Juggler incident.
一个好特工 应该会控制情绪
A good agent controls his temper.
没事的 我爸爸不在这里
Just be glad my dad isn't here.
他对这种事确实有些神经
He gets really psycho about this sort of thing.
嗨 爸爸
Hi Dad.
你记得加利吗 他在我们组织里
Um you remember Gary. He's in our organization.
我在邀请你的女儿跳舞
I was just asking your daughter for a dance.
你会跳舞吗？
You know how to dance?
跳得很好 先生
Fairly well sir.
什么舞？
What kind of dances?
各种舞
All types of dances.
- 探戈怎样？- 可以
- What about tango? - Yes.
- 曼波？- 很好
- Mambo? - Fairly well.
- 伦巴？- 可以
- Rumba? - Yes.
- 恰恰恰？- 7步
- Cha-cha-cha? - Seven steps.
- 波萨诺沃？- 嗯
- Bossa nova? - Mm-hmm.
- 梅伦格？- 当然
- Merengue? - Of course.
华尔兹怎样？
What about waltz?
是 我会华尔兹
Y-Yeah I can waltz.
让我看看
Show me.
好的
Right.
就象那样
Something like that.
好的
All right.
你们可以跳舞
You can go to dance.
看着你姐姐
Watch your older sister.
亚历山德拉？
Alexandra?
怎么？
Yes?
你在那里干什么？
What are you doing in there?
跳舞
Dancing.
你总是带着这些特工吗？
Do you always carry this many Secret Service around?
我爸爸的主意
My dad's idea
他有点… 妄想症
he's gotten a little...paranoid.
那 你能和我… 跳舞吗？
Well would you dance... with me?
不
No.
那好 等一会
All right,hold on a second guys.
2级人物 散开
Level 2 break it up!
为何不？
Why not?
我只跳…
I only dance...
芭蕾
ballet.
什么 不可思议的巧合
What an incredible coincidence.
我也是
So do l.
朱尼 我必须承认
Well Juni I must say,
你是个有才华的男人
you're a man of many talents.
冰山一角
One tries.
呃 请入座好吗？我们要开始了
Uh could you find your seats? We're ready to start.
我必须走了
I must go.
女士们先生们
Ladies and gentlemen,
欢迎美国总统
the president of the United States.
谢谢
Thank you.
我为 欧斯 自豪
I am proud of the O.S.S.
还有他们新建的特工小子分队
and their newly formed Spy Kids division.
他们昨天的成就
For their outstanding accomplishments yesterday.
加利 和 杰蒂 吉格斯
Gary and Gerti Giggles
不仅救了我的女儿…
not only saved my daughter...
他在说什么？我救了她
What is he talking about?! I saved her!
朱尼…
Juni...
但更重要的是
But more importantly,if not most importantly,
他们安全地找回了魔酷光碟
they safely retrieved the Transmooker device
是我女儿在我办公室 在那前一天
that my daughter accidentally took from my office
偶然拿走的
earlier that day.
现在 我荣幸地宣布
Now it is my great pleasure to announce
欧斯新的长官…
the new director of the O.S.S....
格瑞利
Gregor-
… 唐纳根·吉格斯
...Donnagon Giggles.
加利 和 杰蒂 吉格斯
Gary and Gerti Giggles
是我们所需要特工
are the kind of agents we need
给欧斯注入生气
to turn the O.S.S. around.
我荣幸地授与他们
I am proud to award them
1级人物徽章
these Level 1 badges,
- 什么？- 这使他们可执行真正的任务
- What? - which will enable them to take on real missions,
具有挑战性的 象尤卡达任务
something challenging,like the Ukata assignment.
太好了
Yes!
我要那个任务 这不公平
I wanted that assignment. This is so unfair.
我荣幸地宣布
I am proud to claim them
他们是我们组织中的 高级特工小子
as our organization's top Spy Kid operatives!
事情有点不对
Something's not right.
并且我荣幸地
And I'm also proud
宣布 当然
to claim them of course,
他们是我的孩子
as my children.
这全不对劲
This is all wrong.
为我们特工小子干杯
To our Spy Kids.
- 为特工小子 - 为特工小子
- To our Spy Kids. - To our Spy Kids.
为特工小子
To our Spy Kids.
这
This ugh! Ohh.
四周警戒
Secure the perimeter!
安眠药
Sleepers.
他们在找魔酷光碟
They're after the Transmooker device!
抓住他们
Take 'em down.
- 拉 - 拉
- Pull! - Pull!
- 哇 - 哇
- Whoa! - Whoa!
走开 小子
Get off squirt.
还给我
Give me that back!
- 你没事吧 先生？- 没事
- You all right sir? - Yeah.
过来
Come here!
朱尼 放开他
Juni get off of him!
不 不 他们拿走了魔酷光碟
No no. They took the Transmooker device!
他们拿走了魔酷光碟
They took the Transmooker device!
以下特工小子人员
The following Spy Kid cadets
请向特异功能处报到
please report to the psychic abilities seminar
麦克-卡德纳斯 丹尼尔德鲁兹
Mike Cardenas and Daniel Duluth.
- 又该我了 - 是吗？
- It's my turn too. - Are you sure?
那 你的名字是？
All right your last name is?
等一会
Hold on a second.
我已经拿到了魔酷光碟
I had the Transmooker in my hand,
但是朱尼
but you know Juni
他想自己拿到它
he wanted to claim it for himself.
- 好了 知道了 谢谢你 儿子 - 好的
- Okay that should do it. Thank you son. - Right.
如果魔酷光碟落入坏人手里…
If that Transmooker device falls into the wrong hands...
我们就完了
we're doomed.
谢谢 总统先生 那不会的
Thank you Mr. President. That'll be all.
我们完了
We're doomed!
明白了 先生
Understood sir.
给
Here.
暗黑破坏王神奇秀
"Floop's Fooglie"...
主演 迷你安…
Starring Minion...
卡门…
and Carmenita...
谢谢
Thanks.
我被开除了
I was fired.
我知道
I know.
我看了 欧斯的数据档案
I hacked into the O.S.S. data files
看到了消息
and saw the news.
我想这或许是我的错
It was probably my fault,I suppose.
对不起
I'm sorry.
算了 就那么回事
Well I guess that's that.
我们去树房 我有个主意
Let's go to the tree house. I got an idea.
我总是在想在这里
I guess I could always set up
搞一个小侦探社什么的
a small detective agency out here or something.
你又在想"小"了 朱尼
You're thinking small again Juni.
这老树房
The old tree house
需要一个直升飞机起降台
needs another helicopter pad.
它需要漆一下 这才是它需要的
It needs a paint job,is what it needs.
你的名字？
Your name?
卡门·"天使脸魔鬼身"·克兹
Carmen Elizabeth Juanita Echo Sky Brava Cortez.
你的名字？
Your name?
朱尼·"叛逆胖小子"·克兹
Juni Rocket Racer Rebelde Cortez.
你知道…
You know...
我有点想退休
I'm kind of looking forward to retirement,
去实现一些以前的梦想
get back to all the projects and dreams I left behind.
行了 朱尼
Oh stop it Juni.
你到底想不想把工作要回来？
Look do you want your job back or not?
这就是了 恢复2级
That's right reinstated Level 2.
这样我们就能拿回失去的魔酷光碟
So now we can get back the missing Transmooker.
怎么做？
How?
好象加利和杰蒂要去接受
Looks like Gary and Gerti are about to get briefed
尤卡达任务了
on the Ukata assignment.
我们应该去听听
We should listen in.
小绿瓢 还在你办公室吗？
Is R.A.L.P.H. still at your office?
若他们还没有把它清理掉 就会在
If they haven't cleaned it out yet.
小绿瓢 去下达简令室
R.A.L.P.H.,get to the briefing room.
我们要你监听加利和杰蒂
We need you to spy on Gary and Gerti.
不要让人看到你
Make sure no one sees you.
马达加斯加岛海岸
There is a Bermuda Triangle of sorts
有一个类似百慕大魔鬼三角
off the coast of Madagascar.
你们或许记得 在那里
As you may remember,this is an area
我们的一些货物消失了
where some of our O.S.S. cargo ships have been disappearing.
干得好 小绿瓢
Good boy R.A.L.P.H.
生还者们
The survivors of these disappearances
述说了幻觉似的故事
tell delusional tales
一个奇怪生物居住的神秘的岛
of a mysterious island populated by strange creatures.
显然 那里附近没有陆地
Obviously no land mass is located anywhere near there,
所以 这故事没人相信 特工也被开除了
so these tales were dismissed and the agents fired.
然而…
However...
拿走魔酷光碟的磁性船
the magnet ship that captured the Transmooker device
最后一次出现在那里
was last seen in this same area.
所以 我们需要一只小船
So we need a small ship,
由2位小特工驾驶
piloted by two small agents
去近处看一看
to go in and take a closer look.
如果你们发现什么不寻常
If you find anything out of the ordinary,
就返回
you return,
回到这里报告
you report it back here.
- 我们接受 - 我们接受
- We accept. - We accept.
我们肯定接受
You bet we accept.
回来 小绿瓢 干得好
Come home R.A.L.P.H. Good work.
是个了不起的任务
It's a great assignment,
但加利和杰蒂得到了 我却被开除
but Gary and Gerti have it,and I'm fired.
我把你召回 欧斯
And I'm reassigning you to the O.S.S.
- 别说你黑进去 - 已经做了
- Don't tell me you're hacking into - Already done.
2级状态
Level 2 status
召回了
reinstated.
卡门 你不能这么做
Carmen you can't do this.
我已经做了 我还要再做点事
I already did it. I'd take it one step further.
分派我们去执行尤卡达任务
We're assigning ourselves to the Ukata assignment.
我给加利和杰蒂另派个任务
I'm programming a new destination for Gary and Gerti.
现在 我也要参与进去了
Now that,I got to be a part of.
你的名字
State your name please.
加利·吉格斯
Gary Giggles.
拒绝
Access denied.
它知道你不是他
It knows you're not him.
确认
Confirmed.
新目标？
New destination?
去…
How about...
戈壁沙漠怎么样？
Gobi Desert?
别这样 朱尼
Stop it Juni.
怎么了？
What?
不想让你的男友去那么远？
Don't want your boyfriend to go so far away?
他不是我男友
He's not my boyfriend.
那好吧
Okay then.
目标确认
Destination confirmed.
好了 然后我们要做什么？
There. What did we just do again?
我们要把魔酷光碟拿回来
We're gonna get the Transmooker device back
为你洗清罪名
so we can clear your name.
我们必须在别人发现以前
We just have to solve the case
完成这项任务
before anybody finds out what we're up to.
你一块来吗？
Are you with me?
好的
Okay.
那我们走
Then let's go.
你好？
Hello?
嗨 你们在上面干什么？
Hey what are you doing up there?!
抱歉 我们以为是其他人
Sorry we thought you were somebody else.
谁给你的钥匙？
Who gave you a key?
你忘了谁建的这房子？
Did you forget who built you this place?
下来吧
Come down from there.
我给你们带来了最新发明的小机件
I brought you all-new gadgets.
看看吧 最新的间谍手表
Check it out the very latest spy watch
是个信息中心
total communication center,
就在你的手腕上
right there on your wrist.
大哥大 因特网 卫星电视
Cellphone lnternet access,satellite TV
什么都有
you name it.
它除了时间什么都能告诉你
That baby will do everything but tell you what time it is.
没时间显示？
It doesn't tell time?
没有 它装的东西太多了
No there was so much stuffed into it,
没地方装表了
there was no more room for the clock.
酷
Cool.
你确认这是最新的吗？
Are you sure these are new?
我们不能带着过时的设备执行任务
We can't be running around with outdated equipment.
闭上眼睛 伸出手来
Close your eyes and hold out your wrist.
我要给你们
I'm gonna give you
要永远戴着的小玩意
the one gadget you should always carry.
橡胶带？
A rubber band?
不 它是马雀弹性圈
No it's a Machete elastic wonder.
是橡胶带
It's a rubber band.
是 但它也是世上最伟大的玩意
Yeah but it's also the world's greatest gadget
有999种用途…
999 uses...
重要的是
and the important thing
你必须想出它的用途… 用这个
is you have to figure out what those uses are...with this.
他说的对
He's right.
第一种用途 漂亮和手镯
Use number one a stylish bracelet.
第二种用途…
Use number two...
我要用这赚大钱
I'm gonna make a fortune with these.
你肯定这管用吗？
Are you sure this is going to work?
冷静些
Just be cool.
若有人发现 你就做后备
As far as anybody knows,you're back on the force.
嗨 菲利克斯叔叔
Hey Uncle Felix.
噢
Oh.
我不是你叔叔
I'm not your uncle.
我知道 只是那样称呼方便些
I know. It's just easier to call you that.
你不在意 是吗？
Um you don't mind do you?
当然不
Of course not.
欢迎你回来 朱尼
Well welcome back Juni.
上面说你被召回了
Says here you were reinstated.
当然了 对不？
Sure does doesn't it?
他在同一天被开除又被召回
He was fired and rehired all in the same day.
是了
Okay.
我去拿间谍龙5号的钥匙
Let me bring up the keys to the DragonSpy Five.
凯克
Cake.
6点方向
6 o'clock.
你的新的玩意很好呀 卡门
Wow. You're looking good with the new gear Carmen.
- 是最新式的 - 很酷…
- Their latest stuff. - Very cool...
是我们数周前戴的
only we had that weeks ago.
这才是最新的
Here's what's really new.
纳米技术
Nanotechnology
你带的所有东西 都在我手腕上了
everything you're wearing is right here on my wrist.
它超准确 又很轻
It's superaccurate and oh so light.
甚至显示时间
It even tells time.
你怎么得到的？
How did you get that?!
这是样品 朱尼
Well it's all prototype,Juni.
你不能带上生产线的东西执行任务
You can't be running around with those mass-produced gadgets.
因为任何人都有了
Just means everyone's got them.
我总是带样品
I always go with the prototype.
当然 他们有点… 毛病
Sure,they're a little...buggy,
但我能应付
But I can deal.
我-我出欧斯回家的时候
I-I accidentally squashed him
不小心踩扁了它
on my way out of the O.S.S. building.
对不起了
Sorry about that.
但 他也过时了
He was outdated anyway,
只当是安乐死吧
so think of it as a mercy killing.
加利和杰蒂 吉格斯
Gary and Gerti Giggles,
你们的任务是SElKJu9
you have assignment SElKJu9.
祝你好运
Good luck.
别让那过时的玩意伤了你
Don't hurt yourselves with that outdated gear.
记住 一个特工和他的装备一样好
Remember an agent is only as good as his gadgets.
什么？
What?
你们是尤卡达任务？
You have the Ukata assignment?
很好
Very nice.
你会喜欢的
You'll love it.
谢谢 菲利克斯叔叔
Thanks Uncle Felix.
我不是你的叔叔
I'm not your uncle.
噢 好潜艇
Oh nice sub.
欢迎来到间谍龙 DLX
Welcome to the DragonSpy DLX.
看起来他们越来越复杂了
Seems like they get more and more sophisticated
每个月如此
each month.
什么都是自动的
Everything is automated!
现在为您剪鼻毛
Now picking your nose.
小弟弟
Ugh little brothers.
来看看有什么午餐 这可是完成任务的养料
Let's check our lunchboxes for mission updates.
对不起 小绿瓢
Sorry R.A.L.P.H.
你是最好的间谍
You were the best spy on the force.
朱尼 别管它 他死了
Juni leave it alone. He's dead.
全拜你那朋友加利所赐
Thanks to your buddy Gary.
那是无意的
It was an accident.
你喜欢他且相信他？
You like him and believe him?
我不喜欢他… 不是很喜欢
I don't like him... that much.
加利是个坏家伙 卡门
Gary's a bad guy Carmen.
或许我知道
Maybe I know that.
我想我可以改变他
I think I can change him.
不明白你
I do not understand you.
你永远不会
And you never will.
法国炸鸡？
French fry sir?
给我
Gimme that!
奇怪 神秘岛的故事
Strange, tales of a mysterious island,
消失的船 神秘的物种
disappearing ships,mysterious creatures,
并且 欧斯的货物
and yet,no information anywhere
磁性飞船 没有任何信息
on the O.S.S. cargo or the magnet ship.
唐纳根在那里干什么？
What's Donnagon doing there?
他那时还不是 欧斯的长官
He wasn't O.S.S. director yet.
这是原来 欧斯的秘密
These are old O.S.S. secrets.
我知道一个我们可以求助的人
And I know just the person we can call for advice.
谁？
Who?
什么？
What?
何时？
When?
哪里？
Where?
谁？ 什么 何时？
Who? What? When?
- 哪里？ - 为什么？
- Where? - And why?
我乐于
I delight in
- 我要找的答案？ - 寻找
- What... Do I intend to find? - Find
这一次？
This time?
到处跑 跳下来
Run around! Jumping down!
跳起来…
Bounce and bound and...
找另一个方法
Find another way to duck and hide
这个小岛…
This isle of...
梦
Dreams
喂？
Hello?
是的
Yes.
请等一下
One moment please.
停
Cut!!
你是谁 请再说一遍？
Who is it again?
朱尼 克兹
Juni Cortez!
我能为你做点什么？
What can I do for you?
我是说 你为我做了很多事情
I mean,you've done so much for me.
你们的机器人复制品
Your robot counterparts
深深地打动了我
are the surprise hit characters of my show!
问个好
Say hello.
- 你好 - 你好
- Hello - Hello
事实上 卡门想和迷你安先生谈一谈
Actually Carmen wants a word with Mr. Minion.
噢 他在这
Oh. He's right here.
迷你安正在研究4合1的协调问题
Minion is practicing a 4-part harmony.
你有一分钟时间
You have one minute.
你好
Bueno?
你过得怎么样 迷你安？
How you doing Minion?
这里的东西对我来说都提不起精神
Things are a little Floopy around here for my taste,
但还算过得去
but it's a living.
我需要一些情报是关于你感兴趣的的
I need some information on your favorite subject
欧斯
O.S.S. the O.S.S.
我要打个电话
I need to make a call.
好的 你准备好了？
Okay you ready?
尤卡达…
Ukata...
魔酷光碟…
Transmooker...
很难搜索到总统的女儿
The president's daughter is unavailable.
控制
Manage.
按"1"开始记录
Press "1" to record.
你指的是什么？
Mean anything to you?
像是为唐纳根-吉格斯工作的
Smells like the work of Donnagon Giggles.
他是第一个接触到魔酷光碟技术的
He had first contact with the Transmooker technology.
你认为唐纳根这一切的幕后人？
You think Donnagon's the one behind all this?
你正在和一个有四个头的人说话
You're talking to a man with four heads.
相信我 这家伙很坏
Trust me the guy is dirt.
那我们该找谁？
What should we look for?
首先 找到这个岛
First find the island.
然后找到岛人
Then find the lsland Man.
那样就能和唐纳根联系上
That would have been Donnagon's contact.
好的
Okay.
谢谢了 迷你安
Thanks Minion.
做个好姑娘 并帮我好好揍一顿你弟弟
Be a good girl and swat your brother for me.
哦 我会的
Oh I will.
出问题了 控制方向
Something's wrong! Take the wheel!
走了 好运
Got to go. Good luck!
减速 我们接近目的地了
Slow down! We're nearing destination zone.
有效航程设置正确…
The radius where all the disappearances occurred is right...
这儿
Here!
机器停了
We've been shut down!
抓住了
Hold onto something!
所有的动力都关闭了 连紧急电源也是
All power is off even the emergency power.
我的手电筒也不亮了
My flashlight doesn't even work.
我们被困住了 对吗？
We're stuck aren't we?
我们先从这出去
Let's get out of here.
再呼吸
Rebreathers.
我们可以手动控制
You got to do it by hand.
然后？
What next?
不 手 卡门
Nope. Hand Carmen.
难以置信
Unbelievable.
烂东西
Low-tech!
我们走这
Here we go.
我们该用轻的还是重的？
Should we travel light or heavy?
我们也许不会回到这来了
We may not be coming back down here.
我们还是用重的
Let's go heavy.
充气服？
Inflate-a-suits?
我们没有太多的选择
We don't have much choice.
至少呼吸面具还能用
At least the masks work.
我想是真空管的问题 不是电源的问题
I think it's because they're valve-operated,not electrical-based.
太奇怪了
It's so strange.
好运
Good luck.
你也是
You too!
靠近点
Stay close!
- 啊 - 啊
- Ugh! - Ugh!
啊 噢 太好了
Ugh. Oh great.
我胖了
I'm fat!
对于这个事故你怎么看？
Was it supposed to do this?!
其实电路有自动关闭开关
It has an electrical automatic shutoff
就是它出了问题
which didn't work.
还好 壳体破裂之前我们及时出来了
Luckily we ran out of air before the suits exploded.
那么 我们可以笑了
Well we can still laugh.
笑什么？
At what?
不管怎样 想象一下加利和杰蒂在干什么
At whatever you can imagine Gary and Gerti are doing
对
right about now.
杰蒂 我们在哪？
Gerti where are we?!
那…
Well...
按照我显示的坐标
according to my coordinates,
我们…
we are...
我想
I think that
骆驼粪坑
Camel poop!
某人要付出代价
Someone's gonna pay!!
克兹姐弟…
Cordezes...
我喜欢你的新办公室
I like your new office.
太小了… 舒服
It's smaller...cozy.
特别… 小
Especially...smaller.
噢
Oh!
这么多成功的任务
So many successful missions.
令人惊奇 不是吗？
Amazing isn't it?
记得这个吗？
Remember this one?
哦 那是哪一个任务？
Oh. Which mission is that?
墨西哥
Mexico.
当然
Of course.
嗯
Hmm.
事实上 那是我们唯一的
Actually,that was the one mission
没有完成的任务
we never accomplished.
英格丽…
Ingrid...
不要再惊动你的父母
don't start with your parents again.
很好笑你会提起他们
It's funny you should mention them.
不 每当我提起你的父母恰恰不好笑
No. When I mention your parents it is the exact opposite of funny.
我们从未得到他们的祝福还困扰着你吧？
Doesn't it bother you that we never got their full blessing?
- 坦白地说 你应该另外找个机会给他们看 - 好的 好的
- Frankly you deserve another chance to show them - All right all right.
你愿意的话可以邀请他们 但我不会在这
Invite them if you want,but I won't be here.
告诉他们我... 我有其他任务
Tell them that I had a I had to go on another mission,
说 我们在月球上有点小问题
that that we're having a little problem on the moon.
我父亲喜欢月球
My father loves the moon.
你已经邀请了他们 对吗？
You invited them already,didn't you?
嗯… 定义一下"邀请"
Mm...define "invite."
克兹
Cortezes.
怎么？
What?!
我有些坏消息 我可以进来吗？
I have some bad news. May I come in?
- 啊 - 啊
- Uh. - Uh.
- 当然 - 是的
- Certainly sir. - Yes sir.
好
Great.
他在这
Here he is.
我们派出的两个特工小子
Two of our Spy Kid operatives
在尤卡达任务时失去联络
are lost on the Ukata assignment.
你们的孩子就在进行这个任务
Your children had that assignment.
对不起 唐纳根 我们怎么补救？
I'm so sorry Donnagon. How can we help?
事实上 我的孩子们都安全
Actually,my children are safe
在戈壁沙漠的某个地方 我相信
somewhere in the Gobi Desert,I believe.
嗯 我很遗憾说到卡门和朱尼
Uh I'm sorry to say that Carmen and Juni
不知为何 在尤卡达任务
are somehow the ones on the Ukata assignment
某些计算错误
a computing error of some kind.
- 通信？- 没有
- Communications? - None.
他们的飞船
Their DragonSpy ship doesn't show up
雷达和卫星都找不到
on radar or satellite.
格瑞利 英格丽
Greg lngrid,
你们曾经冒着生命危险救过我
you guys risked your lives once before to save me.
让我现在就去
Let me go now
我也要亲自去带你们的孩子回来
and personally bring your children back.
不 谢了
No. Thank you.
谢谢 唐纳根
Thank you Donnagon,
但是 不好意思 我们必须自己去做这件事
but respectfully,we have to do this ourselves.
如果你能为我们提供战术后援
If you could provide tactical backup
和监控支持的话
and surveillance support of our efforts,
我们马上就出发了
we'll leave immediately.
好的
Okay yeah.
啊 英格丽…
Uh lngrid...
我知道不合时宜 但 嗯…
I know this may be a bad time but um...
你父母来了
Your parents are here.
但你们告诉我你们要下星期二才来的
But you guys told me you were coming next Tuesday.
这是一个非常危险的任务
This is a very dangerous assignment,
你们必须在此等候
and you have to wait here.
那 我们需要帮助
Well we want to help.
别担心
Don't worry.
你教会了我知道的每一件事
You taught me everything I know.
是的…
Yes...
但是并不是每一件事我们都了如指掌
but not everything we know.
当然 爸爸 几小时后再见
Of course not Dad. See you in a few hours.
谢谢 亲爱的
Thanks honey.
我还是不喜欢他
I still don't like him.
朱尼… 朱尼…
Juni... Juni...
那岛原来就在那吗？
was that there before?
一分钟前才有的 不是吗？
That wasn't there a minute ago was it?
你在踢我？
Are you kicking me?!
我离你远着呢
I'm way over here!
我觉得有什么东西在碰我的脚
I felt something against my foot.
我的下面有什么东西 快看看
There's something under me! Come look!
我什么都没看到 朱尼
I don't see anything Juni.
我们还是努力先靠岸吧
Let's just concentrate on getting to shore.
好吧 大约有200码远
Okay it's about 200 yards.
如果我们用脚轮流滑水
If we kick steadily at one foot per kick,
我们总会到岸的 嗯…
we'll reach it in um...
25分钟？
25 minutes?
我不知道
I don't know.
我的计算器也坏了
My calculator doesn't work.
- 哇 - 哇
- Whoa! - Whoa!
朱尼 你干什么了？
Juni what did you do?!
气体从充气衣跑出来了
The air's coming out of our suits!
我们朝岸边去
We're heading towards shore!
"笨重的行进"
"Travel heavy"!
好主意
Good idea!
好吧
All right.
休息一下 啊 啊
Give it a rest. Ugh. Ugh.
好吧 我们要找个露营点
Okay we're gonna set up a campsite,
把帐篷支起来生堆火
put up the tent,build a little fire.
然后煮点吃的？
And roast marshmallows?
真不敢相信
I can't believe this!
怎么了？
What happened?
没什么 就是这个
Nothing that's just it.
这个是假定的营火
That was supposed to make an instant campfire,
而那个是假定的帐篷
and that was supposed to make a shelter.
这些东西都不能用了
None of our gadgets work.
你是说我们必须自己手动干活？
You mean we have to use our heads?
对
Yes.
天
Ouch.
大大的办公室…
Big office...
欧斯控制中心
Director of the O.S.S.'s office.
真大
Big.
你找到着强大能量的来源没有？
Did you find the source of equal or greater power?
是从岛的北部发出来的
It emanates from the north side of the island.
你找到岛人的位置了？
Have you located the lsland Man?
他就在地下的某个位置
He's somewhere underground.
那好 开始挖掘 我在路上了
Yeah well start digging. I'm on my way.
快点 朱尼
Come on Juni.
我们去查看一下这个岛
Let's go check out the island.
我刚架好吊床
I just set up camp.
看到没有？
See?
我确定加利也在这
Sure wish Gary was here.
他一定想找出这背后的一切
He'd want to find out who was behind all this.
哦 好了
Aw man!
好吧 我们走
All right let's go.
喔
Wow!
这地方真惊奇
This place is amazing!
看看那块石头
Check out that rock!
像个大热狗
Looks like a hot dog.
嗯
Uh-huh.
好了 我看够了 我们回海滩
Well I've seen enough. Let's go back to the beach.
什么？
What?
听
Listen.
啊
Ugh!
这儿肯定有厉害的人物
Somebody here has power.
我们得找出来是什么人 他要干什么
We need to find out who and for what.
目的地 尤卡达
Destination Ukata.
评估飞行时间 一分钟计算
Estimated time of arrival one minute and counting.
我们现在有多快？
How fast are we going?
85节
85 knots.
那好… 再快一点
Well...go faster.
很乐意
With pleasure.
快点
Faster.
不能快了
Can't go faster.
快点
Faster.
我超越速度极限了
I broke the fast thingy.
快点
Faster!
好了…
All right...
然后呢？
now what?
真令人恐怖
This is terrific.
你知道 这真不错
You know,this is just great.
这次你真的做到了 杰蒂
You really did it this time Gerti.
你在踢我？
Are you kicking me?
没有 我离你很远
No. I'm way over here,cheese ball.
我要杀了这些怪物
I'm gonna zap that sucker to bits!
到这来
Come here!
等一下
Wait!
留给克兹他们吧
Save it for the Cortezes.
对…
Yeah...
好主意
Excellent idea.
找不到他了 我刚看他从这穿过去
I don't get it! I saw it go through this wall.
你的看法呢 朱尼？
What's your assessment Juni?
我倒是认为为我的胃找点食物会比较好
I'd think better with food in my belly.
我想我们应该到那上面去查看一下
I think we should go up there and check it out.
那上面 火山顶？
Up there to the top of the volcano?
是的
Yep.
就算我的微型机械手还能用 我也不去
Not even if my micrograpplers were working.
加利肯定够胆子上去
Gary would be brave enough to do it.
不会的
Nope.
不管你说什么也改变不了我的决定
Nothing you can say can change my mind.
- 你刚才说什么？- 我什么也没说
- What did you just say? - I didn't.
赶快跑到顶上去
Race you to the top!
啊 火山
Ah. Volcano.
朱尼 往后站
Juni stay back.
不是活火山
It's not active.
朱尼
Juni!
噢
Ohh!
你还在等什么？
What are you waiting for?!
赶快把我拉上去
Get me out of here!
如果我的自动牵引器还能用的话
If my auto retractor was working,
我会把我们俩都拉上去的
I'd get us both back up there!
啊 好的 我要抓住你的手
Uh. Okay. I'm gonna grab your hand.
好了 喔
Okay. Ohh!
我的手机
My cellphone!
怎么停下来了？
Why'd you stop?!
不对劲？
Something wrong?
闭上你的眼睛
Close your eyes.
为什么？
Why?
朱尼
Juni!
什么？
What?!
很抱歉
I'm sorry!
我们下降了多久了？
How long have we been falling?
我不知道
I don't know.
我的手表停了
My watch doesn't tell time.
你猜呢？
Best guess?
我想有差不多3小时了
I'd say about three hours.
我觉得有4小时
Feels like four.
这个时候你还能想着吃？
How could you be eating at a time like this?!
当你下落的时候你感觉怕吗？
You know that tickling sensation you get when you fall?
当然
Of course.
从第一个小时以后我就没什么了
That pretty much went away after the first hour.
哇
Whoa!
Waah!
啊
Aah!
怎么回事？
What happened?!
我不知道 我们在漂浮
I don't know! We're floating!
你是谁？
Who are you?
- 你看到什么了？- 那边 藏起来了
- Do you see something? - Over there hiding.
你们要干什么？
What do you want?
我要下来
I want to get down.
我是卡门·克兹 欧斯的特员
I'm Carmen Cortez,special agent of the O.S.S.
我叫罗梅罗
I'm Romero,
我是这个岛的唯一居民…
sole inhabitant of this island of Leeke Leeke...
… 唯一的人类居民
...sole human inhabitant,that is.
你们是？
And you are?
又累又饿
Tired and hungry.
很高兴认识你们 又累又饿
Nice to meet you,Tired and Hungry.
- 啊 啊 噢 噢 - 小心 你会弄坏我的岛的
- Ahh! Ugh! Ohh! Ohh! - Careful! You'll crush my island!
抱歉
Sorry.
我们刚才下落了4个小时 现在都有点腿脚麻木了
We just fell four hours. We're a little clumsy right now.
你们没有下落 那是你们的幻觉
You weren't falling. It was an illusion.
魔术？
Magic?
科技
Science.
快点 我们必须找个安全的地方
Quickly,we must get somewhere safe!
我是一个遗传学家
I'm a genetic specialist.
我需要一个可以控制的环境来做实验
I needed a controlled environment for my experiments.
我们刚才听到的只是道具？
The creatures we've been hearing?
我的实验…
My experiments...
逃跑的杀人狂
run amok.
发生了什么事？
What happened?
我想我应该多点运气才行
I thought I would make a fortune from it.
孩子们随时随地都可以拥有一个微缩动物园
Kids everywhere would have their own miniature zoos,
在他们的卧室
right there in their bedrooms.
微缩动物园？
A miniature zoo?
人造动物… 在一个方便的水平
God's creatures... on a manageable scale.
难以置信
Unbelievable.
我称它为 罗氏动物园
"Romero's Zoo" I called it "Romero's Zoo"
微缩动物
genetically miniaturized animals.
狮子 老虎 熊 企鹅…
Lions tigers bears,penguins...
猴子
Monkeys.
在桶里的猴子
Monkeys in a barrel.
小心
Careful.
一天 我偶然混合了
One day,I accidentally mixed up
两组或三组实验品
two or three different test tubes
总而言之创造了新的品种…
and created a new species...altogether.
这也是"罗氏动物园二号"…
Romero's Zoo Too...
一个完全崭新的… 微缩动物园…
an entirely new... miniature zoo...
每一个新物种都不同于
where each species is unlike
你以前见过的
any creature you've ever seen.
蝇马？
Horse-fly?
嗯
Uh-huh.
呃… 鱼猫
Uh...cat-fish.
蛛猴？
Spider-monkey?
牛蛙
Bull-frog.
小心
slizzards.
- 哇 - 远离他们
- Whoa. - Stay away from those.
并且 我已经开始考虑
And so I started to think,
"如果我只将他们造得这么小一点点 "
"lf only I could make them all a wee bit bigger,"
对于孩子们来说
You know for kids with meatier hands.
这些都是错误的
That's where things went very wrong.
我对他们使用了成长血清
I applied a growth serum,
他们便不受控制的疯狂成长
and they took to it all too well.
哇
Whoa!
不
N-N-No!
啊 啊 不
Aah! Aah! No!
从那以后我就被困在这里了
And I've been locked up in here ever since.
我再也不敢出去了
I'm afraid to go out there again.
它们不止一次的想吃掉我
They've tried to gobble me up on more than one occasion.
为什么他们不把我放在眼里？
Why do they despise me so?
我创造了他们
I created them.
你认为…
Do you think...
上帝呆在天堂
God stays in Heaven
因为他 也生活在恐惧里
because he too,lives in fear
因为他也创造了…
of what he's created...
地球上的这儿？
here on Earth?
不要这样看着我
Stop looking at me like that.
我不是笨蛋
I'm no loon.
我仍然想知道的是
What I'm still trying to figure out
为什么这个岛没有公布于世？
is why this island doesn't show up
甚至在我们最先进的人造卫星上也找不到？
on even our most advanced satellites.
我知道了一道"保护衣"以防止被发现
I created a cloaking device to shield my island from curious eyes.
任何电子辐射都在半径一英里的范围内
Anything electronically powered that comes within a mile radius
超过了就关闭了
instantly shuts down.
所有的雷达都被我用"替换法"忽略了
Any radar that passes over me is displaced,
在我的岛上创造幻想是不存在的
creating the illusion that my island doesn't exist.
魔酷光碟设备
The Transmooker device.
你们怎么知道的？
How did you know?
你的"保护衣"设备很让人垂涎三尺
Your cloaking device is highly coveted.
所有的人都想尝试一下
People everywhere are trying to get their hands on it.
你确认这里除了我们就没有其他人了？
Are you sure we're the only humans here?
他们在那
There they are
根据他们的大小来判断 是两个小孩
two children,judging by their size.
这是什么？
What is this?
微缩岛屿
It's a miniature of the island.
岛中央的火山为我创造的一切
The center point of the volcano provides a gravitational basis
提供了重力基础
for which my miniature creatures
可以有序的排列他们更大的克隆副本
can line up exactly to their larger clone counterparts.
那么 无论怎样 你的微缩创造都在这个模型上
So wherever your miniature creatures are on this model,
而外面的却是巨大的？
it's where the bigger ones are outside?
正确 我可以通过这个办法确认它们的行动路线
Correct. I can keep track of their whereabouts this way.
看到没？
See?
这两个入侵的小孩正在被追击
The two intruder children are being chased by a slizzard.
- 加利和杰蒂 - 快跑
- Gary and Gerti. - Leave 'em.
我们必须去帮助他们
We have to go help them!
他们不应该上岛来刺探这的一切
They shouldn't be snooping around my island to begin with!
- 我同意你的说法 - 我们必须去帮助他们
- I'm with you dude. - We have to help them.
我才不出去那里 我会被吃掉的
I'm not going out there! I'll be eaten!
你这个怪人
What a bizarre man.
- 救救我们 - 救命 救救我们 救命
- Help us! - Help!
来人啊
Somebody!
你们在下面干什么？
What are you guys doing down there?!
你问得真好笑 快把我们拉上来
That's real funny clown. Get us out!
我们本来可以用微型机械手
We tried to activate our micrograpplers,
但却不灵了
but they didn't deploy!
在这里什么也用不了
Nothing works here.
好了 我们知道这些了
Yeah we know that now. Thanks for the update,carrot top.
- 朱尼 回来 他们需要我们的帮助 - 噢 我会帮他们的
- Juni come back. They need our help. - Oh I'll help them.
我会把他们拉上来的
I want to get him back over here
这样才能稳住我自己
so I can push him back over myself.
- 快点 - 快点
- Hurry up. - Come on.
这儿 加利
Here Gary.
把手给我
Gimme your hand.
谢谢 卡门
Thank you Carmen.
这儿 杰蒂…
Here Gerti...
把手给我
gimme your hand.
等会我爸爸就来了
Just wait till my father gets here.
你爸爸也来了？
Your father's coming?
你要带我们去哪里 卡门？
Where are you taking me now Carmen?
继续走
Hold on.
为什么你还要继续躲藏？我们都是孩子 不是妖怪
Why are you still hiding? We're kids not monsters.
有什么区别？
What's the difference?
放松点 他们是欧斯特员
Relax. They're O.S.S. agents as well.
- 一级 - 他们是唐纳根的孩子
- Level one. - They're Donnagon's kids.
唐纳根干员？
Donnagon? Agent Donnagon?
你们为欧斯工作？
You work for the O.S.S.,don't you?
我在为一个叫唐纳根的人工作
I work for a man named Donnagon.
这家伙是谁？
Who is this guy?
- 唐纳根对你的创造不感兴趣 - 为什么？
- Donnagon's not interested in your creatures. - Why not?
魔酷光碟设备藏在你的岛上-
The Transmooker device that hides your island
那才是唐纳根真正想要的
that's what Donnagon really wants.
听起来他的确不感兴趣
That's not nearly as interesting.
现在唐纳根是欧斯的头了
Now that Donnagon's head of the O.S.S.,
他有能力从你这带走设备
he has the power to take it from you.
你胡说些什么 朱尼？
What are you babbling about now Juni?
你们拿走了魔酷光碟
The Transmooker you took
从总统的女儿手上拿走的
from the president's daughter Gary.
那只是个原型
It was just a prototype.
真正的魔酷光碟设备藏在这个岛上
The real Transmooker device is here on this island.
它甚至更有能量
It's even more powerful
并且可以停止这行星上的一切科技
and can shut down all technology on the planet.
你说你爸爸也在来这的路上了
You said your father's on his way.
我想它是来寻找魔酷光碟的
I think he's coming to pick it up.
你们都是说谎的家伙
You're all liars.
你们认为你们这么说我就会叫我爸爸回去？
Do you really think you're gonna turn us on our own father?
你爸爸叫你们继续这个任务吗？
Did your dad tell you the mission you went on
有给卡门和我的计划？
was just a setup for Carmen and me?
- 为什么没有？- 他有他的原因
- Why not? - He has his reasons.
那就是成为一个好特工的秘诀-
That's what being a good spy is all about
不相信任何人
trust no one.
怎么成为一个特工 我们已经读过了
How to Be a Spy. We've read it.
那 再读一遍
Well read it again.
一个好特工和家人 朋友都没什么联系的
A good spy makes no binding connections with family or friends.
我还是不相信 你呢？
Well I don't believe in that do you?
如果你想成为一名好特工 那就最好相信
If you want to be a good spy,you better believe it.
我爸爸是一个伟大的特工 让我们迅速成长 不是吗？
My father's a great spy,so let's grow up shall we?
不管我爸爸做什么
Whatever my father's done,
都是这世界必须要做的…
it's what it takes to play in the big world...
不管你喜不喜欢
Iike it or not.
快点 杰蒂 我们走
Come on Gerti. Let's go.
他是对的
He's right.
噢 为什么你连一次都不站在我这边？
Oh! Why can't you side with me just once?
没什么两边的问题 你是对的 他也是对的
There are no sides you're right,and he's right too.
那就是成为一个特工的方法
That's what being a spy means.
行了 我不喜欢
Well I don't like it.
- 那么 你放弃吧 - 我会的
- Then quit. - I will.
很好
Yeah right.
唐纳根是对的
Donnagon was right
雷达上没有任何它们的飞船的影子
Their DragonSpy doesn't show up anywhere on radar.
我不喜欢去搜索一艘潜水艇
I am not interested in finding the sub.
记得那年
Remember that year
我亲自给孩子们做牙科手术…
I insisted on doing the children's dental work...myself?
我怎么会忘呢？
How could I forget?
那好…
Well...
当时我给他们装了个微型跟踪器
I installed a nonelectrical tracking device
在牙齿里面
in their teeth
我自己的发明
my own invention.
但我从未测试过
But I haven't been able to test it,
直到…
until...
现在
now.
- 亲爱的 还有用 - 哇…
- Honey it works! - Whoa...
难以置信
Hard to believe.
按照这个来看…
But according to this...
他们在海的中部
They're in the middle of the ocean.
海平面以上
Above sea level.
但他们在地图上哪里呢 那里没有陆地啊
But where they are on the map,there's no land mass.
怎么会这样？
How can that be?
怎么了？
Now what?
我么撞到什么了
Something's got us.
- 啊 - 什么东西？
- Aaah! - What is it?!
你母亲
Your mother.
- 妈妈？- 我们想加入你们
- Mom? - We wanted to join you.
你们疯了？
Are you nuts?
我们需要一艘大船
We needed a bigger boat.
我们也带来了真正的食物
And we brought real food...
不是干冷的压缩食物
none of that freeze-dried stuff you think's so chic.
- 基督徒 - 嗯？
- Son-in-law. - Yeah?
帮帮忙
Make yourself useful.
你们怎么会在这？
Why are you here?
我们想帮你们把孩子们找回来
We wanted to help get our grandchildren back!
啊
Ah-ah!
我们要把我们的孩子找回来
We will get our grandchildren back.
谢谢 噢 等等
Gracias. Oh wait.
- 你嘴唇上有东西 - 什么？
- You've got something on your lip. - What?
- 啊 - 搞定
- Ugh! - Got it.
啊 妈妈…
Uh Mom...
爸爸 我现在是个大姑娘了 我现在能照顾自己 行吗？
Dad I am a big girl now,and I can take care of myself okay?
格瑞利和我 我们会找到我们的孩子的
And Gregorio and l,we can take care of finding our children.
不 看起来你还是没懂
No you don't seem to understand.
这不是你和格瑞利 简单的拯救世界行动
This isn't you and Gregorio simply saving the world again.
这一次 如果你们失败了 我们失去的就太多了
This time we all have much more to lose if you fail.
卡门和朱尼
Carmen and Juni.
你们不能跟着我们
You cannot come with us.
这太危险了
It is too dangerous.
噢 你是说 我们不能控制我们自己 嗯？
Oh you mean uh,we can't handle ourselves huh?
我可以要回我的胡子吗…
May I have my moustache back...
求你了？
please?
如果唐纳根真的上路了…
If Donnagon really is on his way...
… 我们必须毁掉魔酷光碟
...we have to destroy the Transmooker.
问题是在哪里？
Where is it?
岛的另一边 不容易找到
The other side of the island. Not easy to get to.
孤独的旅程
The journey alone
比魔酷光碟本身更危险
is more dangerous than the Transmooker itself.
我确信这点
I made sure of it.
指给我们看
Show us.
你不会出去的 是吗？
You're not going out there,are you?
我们没有太多的选择 不是吗？
We don't have much choice,do we?
和那些妖怪在外面跑？
With those monsters running around?
我不相信它们是妖怪
I don't believe they're monsters.
也许你这么认为
Maybe you shouldn't either.
- 那么 我该相信什么？- 我不知道
- Well what should I believe? - I don't know.
你一直躲在这里
You're always in here hiding.
或许他们倒是想和你在一起作伴呢
Maybe they just wanna be with you.
和我作伴？
Be with me?
吃掉我
They wanna be picking me out of their teeth,
才是它们想要做的
is what they wanna be.
你只是想告诉它们谁是老大
You just gotta show them who's boss.
你们不害怕？
You're not afraid?
你要做的第一件事是…
First thing you gotta do is...
… 从这个深渊掉下去
...fall into this pit.
这是怎么做到的？
How does it work?
看起来 它们是有磁性的
Supposedly,they're run magnetically.
我们要走上一条坚定的路了
We should be able to ride over a determined path.
我们要抢在他们前面拿到魔酷光碟
We have to get the Transmooker before they do.
对
Right.
变蛇
Slizzards.
噢 不
Oh no.
真不错
This is cool.
呃 呃 呃
Ee! Ee! Ee!
噢 啊
Ooh! Uh!
朱尼
Juni!
我想我们应该跳下去
I think we should get off now.
为什么？
Why?
相信我
Trust me!
跳
Jump now!
加利和杰蒂
Gary and Gerti.
我告所过你他们肯定会跟踪我们的
I told you they were following us.
你有一条新留言
You have one new message.
留言一…
Message one...
你好 亚历山德拉 是我
Hello Alexandra,it's me
朱尼·克兹间谍
agent Juni Cortez.
我在执行任务…
I'm on a mission...
我知我不该
I know I shouldn't be.
但我有个好主意关于你父女
But I had an idea for you and your father.
直接令他知你想和他说话
Simply tell him you need to talk to him.
告他这并不急
Tell him it's nothing urgent,
但终有一日将十万火急
but someday it might be urgent.
你该立刻打开通讯线路
And you need to open the communication lines right now.
给我打电话 我会高兴的
So give me a call. Love to hear from you.
现在大约是
And right now it's about
我真蠢 我忘了我的表不报时
Silly me I forgot my watch doesn't tell time.
嗯 那么
Heh. And uh
卡门: 有异常 去掌方向盘
Something's wrong. Take the wheel.
要走了 好运
Gotta go. Good luck!
- 朱尼 - 电脑:消息结束
- Juni! - Computer: End of message.
- 格瑞利 信号表示你在绕圈 - 他不会听你的
- Gregorio the signal requires that you go around it. - He won't listen to you.
- 他不会听你的 妈妈 - 选另一个方向
- He won't listen to you,Mother. - Choose another directi-
他想确定他再次找不到孩子们
He wants to make sure he loses the children again.
若你愿听我们所言
If you would only listen to us and do what we're saying
你跟错方向了
you're tracking them all wrong.
英格丽 告他他跟错方向了
Ingrid tell him he's tracking them all wrong.
爸 妈 我有言在先
Mom Dad,I have told you before,
我再说一遍 没后座驾驶
and I will tell you again no backseat driving.
- 谢谢 - 当格瑞利掌舵 没人能告他该怎么做
- Thank you. - When Gregorio is at the wheel,no one tells him what to do.
转这边 亲爱的
Turn here honey.
对不起
Sorry.
好
Okay.
你确定没看错地图？
You're sure you're reading that map correctly?
坐标符合
The coordinates correspond
卡门和朱尼的 移动位置
to Carmen and Juni's current position.
这是我子女
These are my children.
我将自己找出他们
And I will find them my way!!
神经病
Blah blah blah.
我完全听不懂他所言
I never understand a single word he's saying.
从不
Never.
并非只有我们深陷
Not only were we set up,
但我打赌唐纳根知一切
but I bet Donnagon knew all along
我们接此任务正中他计
that you'd hack your way into taking this assignment.
我也想知道
I was wondering the same thing.
朱尼 张嘴
Juni open up.
怎么？
What?
- 啊 - 爸爸装了跟踪器于我们口中以防我们 走失
- Aah. Aah. - Dad installed these trackers in case we ever got lost.
快 取走我的
Hurry. Take mine out.
我们为何如此做？
And why are we doing this?
若我们走失 谁来相救？
When we get lost,who saves us?
爸妈
Mom and Dad.
现在 若爸妈也不测
Now if Mom and Dad also disappear,
谁阻止唐纳根使用魔酷光碟 装置？
who's gonna stop Donnagon from using the Transmooker device?
唐纳根想将我们一网打尽
Donnagon wants us all together
他可以把我们聚歼于岛
so he can destroy the island and all of us with it.
爸妈 甚至罗梅罗
Mom and Dad even Romero.
所以我们不能令爸妈找到我们…
We can't let Mom and Dad find us...
否则唐纳根将赢
or Donnagon wins.
壮烈牺牲
A big sacrifice.
牺牲家庭
Family is sacrifice.
发生了什么？
What happened?
怎么办 你干了什么？
What did... what did you just do?
失去卡门
We lost Carmen.
和朱尼？
A-And Juni?
朱尼仍在线
Juni's still on-line.
我爱你们
I love you.
不可能
That can't be.
那好 我们该怎么办？
Okay okay. What do we do?
不知道
I don't know.
可能是
Maybe this is like
间谍任务之不想被跟踪
the mission of the spies who didn't want to be found.
你知…
You know...
若他们不想被跟踪
if they don't want to be found,
可能他们陷入危境
maybe their position is compromised.
现在 格瑞利 别跟我说你没 后备计划
Now Gregorio don't tell me you didn't have a backup plan.
英格丽 朱尼是否带着那迷人项链
Ingrid was Juni wearing that charm necklace
去年圣诞节我给他的？
I sent him for Christmas last year?
他从不离身
He never takes it off.
那我们可找到他
Then we got him.
我担心朱尼的安危
I was worried about Juni's well-being,
所以装了个跟踪器在他项链里
so I put a tracer in his necklace.
他在这
There he is.
谢谢 爸
Thanks Dad.
你确信你不愿让我们掌舵？
Are you sure you don't want me to take over the wheel?
我真有趣
I that's funny.
真有趣
It's funny.
继续干活
Back to work.
我们在哪？
Where are we?
嗯…
Well...
离那间地下室不远
not far from the antechamber.
我想就在我们身后
I think it's behind us.
别动
Don't move.
也许它很友善
Maybe it's friendly.
可能不
Maybe it's not.
走
Let's go!
这是个水下洞
It's an underwater cave.
你要行千里方知路在何方
We'll have to go all the way around.
那需一天
That'll take all day.
这必更快
There must be a faster
喔…
Wow...
这是何地？
What is this place?
你想这是真金么？
Do you think that's real gold?
发达了
Gross!
真泥泞
This is so slimy.
我恨泥地
I hate mold.
我可知你所想
I can hear your thoughts.
什么？
What?
你可知我的
And you can hear mine!
我们朱唇未启
Our mouths aren't moving,
但我们可知对方想法
but we can hear what we're thinking.
试着说些什么
Say something.
太奇怪了
How strange.
我们可神交
We can only communicate by thought.
- 魔法 - 嗯
- Magic. - Hmm.
想些什么
Think something.
嗯… 你脚超臭
Um...your feet stink.
我奇怪
I wonder.
好的 这地方真是古灵精怪
Okay this place is really weird.
走
Let's go.
想好
Good thinking.
现在 更像那么回事了
Now this is more like it.
宝藏
Treasure.
骨头
Skeletons.
死人骨头
Dead skeletons.
还有别的么？
Is there any other kind?
这里必是海盗囚房及藏宝处
This must've been where the pirate prisoners and treasure were kept.
这里有个很醒目的项链
This must've been a pretty special necklace
他们生死相守
for them to die fighting over it.
为一个项链狂
One necklace to rule them all
放它回去 朱尼
Put it back Juni!
我还没拿
I didn't take it yet.
我可读你思想 记得么？
I can read your mind,remember?
这是远古邪恶之所
This land is ancient and cursed.
你拿什么必害惨我俩
If you take anything,you'll doom us both.
走
Let's go!
快 我想我找了条出路
Come on! I think I found a way out.
哪条路？
Which way?
不知道 你选右或左？
I don't know you pick right or left?
右
Right.
等等
Wait a minute.
噢 不
Oh no!
我们原地兜圈子
We went in a circle.
什么？
What?
来
Come on.
再试试
Let's try it again.
来 朱尼 我知我们为何至此
Come on Juni! I know what we did wrong.
我们该走左
We've gotta go left.
我或许该还此物
Maybe I should put this back.
噢
Uh-oh.
那些死人骨呢？
Where are the dead skeletons?
啊
Aaaah!
卡门
Carmen!
朱尼
Juni!!
啊
Ugh!
帮帮我
Help me!!
嗯？
Huh?
嗨 骨头
Hey bonehead!
噢 不
Oh no.
为何会这样？
Why is this happening?!
不知
I don't know!
等等
Wait a minute!
你拿了什么 是不是？
You took something,didn't you?!
不 我从你之言
No! Y-Y-You told me not to!
为何我？
Why would l?
噢
Oh!
朱尼
Juni!
卡门
Carmen!!
等
Wait.
啊
Ah.
对不起
I'm sorry.
卡门
Carmen!
你也在这 嗯？
You too huh?
对
Yeah.
你兄在哪？
Where's your brother?
被吃了？
Did he get eaten?
不 他逃出找朱尼
No. He's out there looking for Juni.
你知他是故意砸烂朱尼的小虫
You know he squashed Juni's bug on purpose.
是 我知
Yeah I know.
现在他想去砸烂朱尼
Now he wants to squash Juni.
你不觉得我们该逃出此地？
Don't you think we should get out of here?
噢
Oh.
嗯
Mm-hmm.
卡门
Carmen!
我在作梦
I'm dreaming.
我沉入梦中
I am totally dreaming.
同时我也很饿
And I'm hungry too.
喔
Oh. Oh. Oh.
你要蜜汁火腿和马铃薯片？
You like honey-roasted ham and potatoes don't you?
这是它们之味
That's what flavor this is.
很有营养
Highly nutritious.
富含蛋白质
Packed with protein and essential carbs.
哈
Hyah!
一切半蛛人所需
Everything a growing centaur needs.
别客气
You're welcome.
喔
Ooooohhhh!
噢 你友像被冻干
Well well well. Your friend likes freeze-dried.
我的也是
So does mine.
嗯
Uh!
好 老兄 送他们上路
All right buddy. Let's kick their butts.
哈 放马过来
Heh heh heh. We're waiting.
快来
Come on.
不可令你搞砸我爸的机器 朱尼
Can't let you bust up my dad's machine Juni.
喔
Whoa!
我猜我需砸扁你
So I guess I'll just have to bust you up.
我们可以他们
We can take 'em.
老友 我们可干掉他们
Come on buddy. We can take 'em.
我不认为我们可干掉他们
I don't think we can take 'em!
需试并帮他们
Must try and help them.
必需
Must.
所以 若你父一手造成此事
So even if your dad is behind all this,
你们仍随他左右？
you'd still side with him over what's right?
你怎知谁正谁邪？
Right? How do you ever know what's right?
相信我
Trust me,
时机一到 你就可知道
when the moment comes,you'll know.
我想时机到了
I think that moment's come.
来吧
Come on!
告他们谁是老大
Show 'em who's boss.
是我
I'm the boss.
我是
I'm the
小心
Look out!
啊
Aah!
冲啊 哥们
Forward go man.
快啊 蛛哥 你行的
Come on spidey. You can do it.
耶
Yeah!
噢
Ohh!
你坐骑是废物
Your creature's lame.
如同你
So are you lame-o.
你完了
It's all over for you squirt.
真不幸令姐未在此帮我喝彩
Too bad your dork sister's not here to cheer me on.
呀
Ya-a-a-a-a-a-h!
我不想伤你 卡门
I don't want to hurt you,Carmen.
你这蘑菇头
You're so full of shiitake mushrooms.
喔...
Ooh! Ooh! Ooh!
住手 卡门
Put it down Carmen.
放松
Put it down.
喔
Ohh!
好
Okay.
All right.
杰蒂 来帮手
Gerti,a little assistance here.
别指望我 老哥 你在和女仔打
Don't look at me brother. You're fighting a girl.
你输了
You're gonna lose.
啊
Aah!
我挺你
I'm siding with you.
谢谢
Thanks.
但只此一次
But just this once.
克兹
Cortezes.
你是否愿帮我？
You gonna help me or not?
好 就是这个
Well there it is.
你怎么知道？
How do you know?
因为它如此大和神秘
'Cause it's big and weird and in the middle of the room.
好见解
Good point.
小心 朱尼
Careful Juni!
若你不关好
If you don't shut it down right,
你便把地球推下火坑
you can bring the entire world to an end.
谢谢
Thanks.
我说真的
I'm serious.
我们必需关它
Well we have to shut it down.
关上这
This turns that off.
再关这
And that turns this off.
他说第三个有些机关
He said there's something tricky about the third switch.
看看
Let's see.
晚了 加利 我们先来一步
Too late Gary. We got here first.
站好面墙当乖仔
Just stand up against the wall like a good boy
离我们远点
and leave us alone.
我们带了个朋友来
Nice try but we brought friends this time.
罗梅罗
Romero.
你出来干嘛？
What are you doing outside of your cage?
我不知道
I have no idea.
唐纳根
Donnagon.
你好 间谍
Hello agents.
为我启动它？
Warming it up for me?
准备好合作么 罗梅罗？
Are you ready to cooperate this time Romero?
- 嗯… - 好
- l uh... - Good.
这将痛心… 且简单
This should be pain... and simple.
噢
Oh!
你干什么？
What did you do?
他启动了魔酷光碟
He started the Transmooker!
是你说三个开关
You said three switches.
世界将玩完
The entire world will shut down instantly.
好走 沙士球
Good going cheese ball.
我们可做什么？
What do we do?!
绑好三个开关
You must bind together the three toggle switches.
它不能关闭
It won't stay up!
- 弹性钢丝 - 弹性钢丝
- Machete elastic wonder! - Machete elastic wonder!
这 绑它
Here grab it!
- 啊 - 噢
- Uh! - Oh!
给我 拿来
Give it to me. Give it!
爸…
Dad...
给我
Give it to me.
给我…
Give it to me...
… 或别的
...or else.
给他 卡门
Give it to him Carmen.
它去哪？
Where'd it go?
它去哪儿了？
Where'd it go?!
我不知道
I don't know.
飞猪拿走了
The spork took it.
回它的… 巢
Back to its...nest.
我知它巢在哪 爸爸
I know where the nest is Dad.
我偷了罗梅罗的说明书
I also have Romero's instruction book.
嗨
Hey.
小子
Brat.
来吧
Come on!
就在那大山后
It's just over that big hill.
- 哦 - 哦
- Ohh! - Ohh!
你确定此是正途？
Are you sure this is the right way?
我的表有GPS卫星定位
My watch has a GPS satellite,you dope.
等等
Wait a minute.
这怎么回事？
How can this be?
当你们拆下魔酷光碟
When you took out the Transmooker,
这岛的保护装置就失效了
the island cloaking device was shut down.
我们干嘛用脚走？
Then what are we doing on foot?
回见 罗梅罗
Later Romero.
喂
Whoa!
啊
Aah! Uhh!
这儿
There it is!
上去 老爸 快
Get up there Dad! Come on!
好的 兄弟们
Okay Magna Men,
我们需搭个人梯
we're gonna need a human ladder starting right...here.
卡门
Carmen!
什么？
What?!
间谍需像其装备般优越
An agent's only as good as her gadgets.
他们会到海滩着路
They're heading for the beach.
救命啊
Help! Uh!
那些小鬼说对了
The kid was right.
你干嘛？
What are you doing?
试图引导我们的潜艇浮出
Trying to remote-pilot our submarine to the surface
我可由此逃出升天
so we can get out of here.
开你的GPS看爸妈在哪
. Get on your GPS and see where Mom and Dad are.
这不正常
This can't be right.
这显示他们就在我们环侧
This shows that they're right next to us.
不
Oh no!
不想和祖父母打招呼么
That's no way to greet your grandparents.
来
Come on.
祖父
Grandpa!
啊 朱尼
Ah Juni.
过来
Come here come here.
去哪也别丢下它
Always take this with you wherever you go,
我将永在你身旁
and I'll always be there.
我保证 祖父
I promise Grandpa.
不关你事
Not you guys!
你不想被救
You don't want to be rescued.
你不想活命
You don't want to be saved.
好吧
That's all right.
我们想你们… 可能需要我们
We thought you might... you might need us.
去和你父谈
Go talk to your father.
- 爸 - 嗨
- Dad! - Hey Mom.
- 来吧 爸 看看我 - 两个不愿被找到的间谍？
- Come on Dad. Look at me. - Two spies who didn't want to be found?
- 是 - 是 我如你所想
- Yes. - Yes. I like your thinking.
但你知什么？这些间谍不要我和妈
But you know what? Those spies didn't have me for a mom.
- 来吧 - 谢谢
- Come on. - Thank you.
嗨
Hey.
我永远需要你
I'll always need you.
来
Come on.
卡门·伊丽莎白·朱厄妮塔…
Carmen Elizabeth Juanita...
来你爸这
Come here to your papa.
你还好么？
You okay hon?
好 资料 快
All right. Information. Quick.
好 我们有了魔酷光碟装置
Okay we have the Transmooker device,
但我们需立刻离开此岛
but we need to get off this island right now.
你认为我们来这干嘛？快走
What do you think we're here for? Let's go.
路上我们会解释
We'll explain it on the way.
你不会相信谁是幕后黑手
You won't believe who's behind this.
没有更好的了
It couldn't be any more perfect.
好在非我所想
This better not be what I think it is.
一切都好 是么
It's all being taken care of,all right?
拿魔酷光碟装置 菲利克斯
Get the Transmooker device,Felix.
菲利克斯？
Felix?
抱歉 格瑞利
Sorry Gregorio.
一些力量让一切不同 不是么？
A little power goes a long way doesn't it?
调整它 杰蒂
Reprogram this one Gerti.
我想先把克兹家族
I want to start by wiping the Cortez family
彻底消灭
from the face of the Earth.
菲利克斯叔叔 你怎可这样？
Uncle Felix how could you?
我不是你叔叔
I'm not your uncle.
但我们待你如亲
But we treated you like family.
唐纳根说若我加入他
Donnagon said if I joined him
他不会像对你们般收拾我
He... He wouldn't get rid of me like he's gonna do to you guys.
你怎么可信
You can't argue with that.
你的表还有能量么？
Do you still have power in your watch?
是
Yep.
设好了 爸
Programming complete Father.
谢谢 杰蒂
Thank you Gerti.
试试引导断路器
Try remote-piloting the choppers.
那么 克兹一家 有何遗言？
Well Cortezes,any last words?
我不可在孩子面前说
None that I can say in front of my children.
不提你妈
Not to mention your mother.
- 嗯？- 嗯？
- Huh? - Huh?
来点老套桥段吧 来点老套桥段吧
Let's settle this the old-fashioned way. Let's settle this the old-fashioned way.
啊
Aah!
- 扁他 - 对 上啊
- Kick his butt! - Yeah kick his butt!
- 啊 - 不是那样
- Uh! - Not like that.
头摔
Headbutt.
卧摔
Sleeper hold.
用他的重量对付他
Use his own weight against him.
对
Yeah.
- 噢 - 噢
- Ohh! - Ohh!
啊 起来
Ah get up!
展示你昨夜的雄风
Do what I showed you last night!
后抱
Suplex.
- 我都可以打得更好 - 妈
- Even I can fight better than that. - Mom!
三重后空翻
Triple backflip!
啊？
Uh! Huh?
杰蒂？
Gerti?
你干嘛
What did you...
为什么？
Why?
别让我们开始
Oh don't even get me started.
直到让妈妈知道
Just wait till Mom finds out
你又想称霸世界
you tried to take over the world again.
不 别别别
No. Please please please.
别告你妈
D-Don't tell your mother.
好么？
Please?
啊 你好
Uh hello.
奉总统之令
By order of the president,
你被暂时扣压
you've been temporarily disavowed.
你被炒了
You're fired.
看似我失势了 但我会回来
Looks like I lost this round,but I'll be back.
希望下次你站在好的一边
Hopefully you're on the good side next time.
我们走着瞧 但…
We'll see but...
… 你永不明白
...you never know.
别担心
Don't worry.
他脱线了 我会把他引回正途
He gets out of line,I'll straighten him out.
你去吧 杰蒂
You go Gerti.
你试着救我们
You tried to save us.
为什么？
Why?
因为你们是我亲人
Because you are my family.
你知道…
You know...
地球上没有人
there isn't a man on this Earth
我们认为比我对我们女儿更好
we'd ever think would be good enough for our daughter,
但 嗯…
but um...
你很接近
You come pretty close.
以总统之命
By order of the president,
你们是欧斯新领导
you are the new director of the O.S.S.
恭喜
Congratulations.
嗯
Do...
他们是...
are they...
一级
Level one.
不 谢谢
No thanks.
你不想要？
You don't want it?
我离开欧斯
I'm leaving the O.S.S.
我已见到当顶尖间谍的下场
I've seen what it takes to be a top spy,
我想我会更好的帮助世界
and I think I can be better use to the world
变成最好的… 我自己
by just being the best...me.
但那些酷装备怎么处理？
But what about all the cool gadgets?
我已得到最好装备在此
I got the best gadget right here.
使用第一号 一个精致手镯
Use number one a stylish bracelet.
江湖再见？
See ya around?
是
Yes.
去吧 说
Go ahead. Say it.
什么？
What?
我已告你
I told you so.
从不
Never.
等等
Wait.
谢谢
Thank you.
你做到了 老大
You got it boss.